Oyez Press Records
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Project Records,undated, 1963-1987
  - Gitin, David Legwork
    - Correspondence, TSS, reviews, 1 pc. correspondence from Michael McClure, 1973-1980 (Box 6:148)
    - Photos (used for cover), production notes, copy of paste-ups, ca. 1977 (Box 6:149)
    - production paste-ups, 1977 (Box 17:457)
  - Hill, Lindsay Avelaval
    - page proofs folded as dummy, partial TSS (one poem, 2 versions), contract, correspondence, printing notes, photos, 1974 (Box 6:150)
    - cover layout, 1974 (Box 17:463)
  - Hill, Lindsay Archaeology (work not published by Oyez)
    - TSS, ca. 1976 (Box 6:151)
  - Hiller, Toby
    - Untitled TSS, galley set (work not published), ca. 1979 (Box 6:152)
  - Hiller, Toby Certain Weathers
    - One copy of final book, sample cover proofs, correspondence, unused photos supplied by author, 1987 (Box 6:153)
    - first galleys, 1987 (Box 6:154)
    - second proofs, with 1 pc. printer's correspondence, 1987 (Box 6:155)
  - Hogg, Robert The Connexions
    - 2 sets page proofs (in wrappers), paste-up from galleys, 1966 (Box 6:156)
    - defective copy of finished book, folded proof set, 1966 (Box 6:157)
    - galleys, typescript, contract, correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 6:158)
  - Hooker, Craig Michael Honor Awakens Again
    - TSS, correspondence, 2 photos of author, 1972-1973 (Box 7:159)
    - 3 sets of proofs, 1 pc. correspondence, printer's note, 1972-1973 (Box 7:160)
  - Horsley, James God's Naked Daughter
    - correspondence, TSS, 1972 (Box 7:161)
    - galleys with corrections, page proofs, proofs and designs of cover, photo used for back cover, 1972 (Box 7:162)
  - Horsley, James "The Dance of Dismemberment" (not published by Oyez)
    - copy of TSS, correspondence, 1973 (Box 7:163)
  - Hottel, Christopher The Knives of Dawn
    - correspondence, TSS, 5 sets galleys, 1 set proofs, 1970 (Box 7:164)
    - 2 sets page proofs, sample pages, design notes, blank dummy, set of F & G proofs with cover proof, 1970 (Box 7:165)
  - Kherdian, David Bibliography and Sketch of Michael McClure (work not published by Oyez)
    - author's TSS, correspondence, 1965 (Box 7:166)
  - Kherdian, David David Meltzer: A Sketch from Memory and Descriptive Checklist
    - typescript, galleys, page proofs, 1965 (Box 7:167)
  - Kherdian, David Biographical Sketch and Descriptive Checklist of Gary Snyder
    - galleys, correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 7:168)
  - Korn, Richard "For My Father Dead at Seventy-Eight"
    - proof, design page, printer's setting copy, correspondence, variant versions of typed MS, 1972 (Box 7:169)
  - Korn, Richard Judgment of the Condor
    - correspondence (includes TSS poetry submissions), 1976-1978 (Box 7:170)
    - F & G proofs (1 set 'silverprint' proofs, 1 set 'check' proofs), printer's correspondence, 3 copies of promotional flyer, 1978 (Box 7:171)
    - paste-up camera ready sheets (includes 2 photos with negatives), 1978 (Box 7:172)
  - Korn, Richard and Brugnola, Orlanda Job
    - copy of TSS, paste-ups, copy of finished keepsake booklet, 1981 (Box 7:173)
  - Korn, Richard
    - Secondary material including copies of scholarly articles by Richard Korn, 1964-1978 (Box 7:174)
    - Secondary Correspondence (includes TSS of unpublished poems), 1979-1981 (Box 7:175)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert Hymn to the Gentle Sun
    - correspondence, copy of TSS, proof of biography statement, design sheets, 1966-1967 (Box 7:176)
    - page proofs, extra page proofs, galley sets, undated (Box 7:177)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert "The Jester is Not Always Volunteer"
    - proof of broadside, 1967 (Box 16:445)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert "This Room"
    - original TSS, 2 proofs, finished copy of Christmas Card, print of cover photo, 1970 (Box 7:178)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert Beginning of Lines
    - blank dummy, offset page proofs, printer's bill, 1968 (Box 7:179)
    - copy of TSS, galley set ("2/3"), 1 pc. binder's correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 7:180)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert "The Beginning is the Life is the Word"
    - fold out Christmas card (Oyez keepsake) (variant cover), 1967 (Box 7:181)
    - fold out Christmas card, galleys, correspondence, 1967 (Box 7:182)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert Two Poems
    - TSS, correspondence, 1969 (Box 7:183)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert The Midnight Bridge
    - 2 sets galleys, page proofs, 1971 (Box 7:184)
    - correspondence, copy of cover photo, copy of TSS, blank dummy, set of F & G proofs, 1971 (Box 7:185)
    - cover layout, photos, Oyez Christmas card, 1970 (Box 16:446)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert Mammals of Delight
    - TSS, 2 sets galleys (1 corrected), proofs, flyer, 2 reviews, correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 7:186)
  - Körte, Sister Mary Norbert "Lines Bending" (unpublished broadside?)
    - "second galleys" (one sheet), 1978 (Box 7:187)
  - Lamantia, Philip Touch of the Marvelous
    - correspondence, 1966-1967, 1970 (Box 7:188)
    - partial page proof, ephemera and mailers, photos and design notes for cover, 1966 (Box 7:189)
    - first galleys (corrected by Lamantia) with 3 page typed letter from Lamantia, 1966 (Box 7:190)
    - partial mock-up, partial set of folded page proofs, colophon TSS, 1966 (Box 7:191)
  - Levertov, Denise Summer Poems
    - correspondence, copy of TSS, copy of variant MSS, various sets of partial page proofs, 1967-1969 (Box 7:192)
  - Lummis, Dayton Closets of Mercy
    - production paste-up, photos, ca. 1977 (Box 17:456)
  - Magee, David Course in Correct Cataloguing
    - 2 pcs. printer's correspondence (work reprinted by Oyez?), 1977 (Box 8:193)
  - McClure, Michael The Beard
    - first edition (not intended for sale to the public), ephemera regarding performance history (flyers, reviews, and reviews of subsequent productions), cover proof, correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 8:194)
  - McGaugh, Lawrence A Fifth Sunday
    - correspondence, TSS, galley proofs, cover photo, contract, defective book copy (cover bleeds through), design notes, 1965-1966 (Box 8:195)
  - McGaugh, Lawrence Vacuum Cantos
    - galleys, proofs, partial proofs, printing correspondence, 1969 (Box 8:196)
  - Meltzer, David
    - Secondary Correspondence (I), 1960-1966 (Box 8:197)
    - Secondary Correspondence (II), 1967-1968 (Box 8:209)
    - Correspondence, Ephemera, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 8:210)
    - Secondary Correspondence (III), 1969-1984 (Box 8:211)
    - Untitled TSS ("Allow these fragments..."), 1973 (Box 8:214)
    - Ephemera relating to reading by Meltzer -- 2 flyers, correspondence, printing stamp for tickets, ca. 1974 (Box 9:217)
  - Meltzer, David The Process
    - contract, galleys, photo proof, production correspondence, reviews, 1965 (Box 8:198)
  - Meltzer, David The Dark Continent
    - copies of TSS, author's first carbon MS, 1967 (Box 8:199)
    - correspondence, first galleys, 1967 (Box 8:200)
    - cover proof, galleys, page proofs, dummy, advance sheets, 1967 (Box 8:201)
  - Meltzer, David Rock Tao (never published by Oyez)
    - correspondence, photo of Meltzer, 1966 (Box 8:202)
    - correspondence regarding rights and permissions, 1966-1967 (Box 8:203)
    - sketches by Meltzer (intended for internal artwork), ca. 1967 (Box 8:204)
    - set of page proofs, ca. 1967 (Box 8:205)
    - 1 set uncorrected galleys, 2 partial sets of galleys with corrections, set of corrected galleys, partial page proofs, 1967 (Box 8:206)
    - two sets of corrected galleys, 1967 (Box 8:207)
    - pasted up page proofs, correspondence, 1967 (Box 8:208)
    - cover photographs, ca. 1967 (Box 16:447)
  - Meltzer, David Eden Book (not published by Oyez)
    - copy of TSS, 1970 (Box 8:212)
  - Meltzer, David French Broom
    - page proofs, proof copy in brown wrappers, proof copy in beige wrapper, 1970 (Box 8:213)
  - Meltzer, David Blue Rags
    - copy of TSS, correspondence, dummy with paste-in text, 1974 (Box 8:215)
    - 2 sets proofs marked '1st galleys', 1974 (Box 9:216)
  - Meltzer, David Bolero
    - set of galleys, 1976 (Box 9:218)
  - Meltzer, David Harps
    - rough paste-up of illustration, review, ca. 1976 (Box 9:219)
    - cover layout, ca. 1977 (Box 16:449)
  - Meltzer, David Two-Way Mirror: A Note-Book
    - TSS with typesetting notes (spiral bound), ca. 1976 (Box 9:220)
    - paste-ups, printer's correspondence, 1977 (Box 9:221)
    - correspondence, reviews, print used for dustjacket, with negative, 1977 (Box 9:222)
    - copies of page proofs, 1977 (Box 16:448)
  - Miles, Josephine "Ten New Freedoms" (not published by Oyez)
    - TSS of broadside poem, 1964 (Box 9:223)
  - Miles, Josephine Fields of Learning
    - carbon of TSS, 2 page partial TSS, 3 versions of TSS cover page, 2968 (Box 9:224)
  - Miles, Josephine Civil Poems
    - contract, correspondence, original TSS, corrected page proofs, 1966 (Box 9:225)
    - printer's dummy proof, 4 sets galleys (1 with corrections), ca. 1966 (Box 9:226)
  - Miles, Josephine "Art"
    - Memorial card reprinted from Civil Poems, 1986
  - Naoya, Shiga / Say, Allen / Meltzer, David "Morning Glories" (Oyez Christmas Keepsake, 1977)
    - TSS by Naoya, trans. by Say and Meltzer, ca. 1977 (Box 9:228)
    - original art, ca. 1977 (Box 17:460)
  - Olson, Charles Human Universe (project not completed by Oyez)
    - Correspondence involving Donald Allen and Andrew Hoyem regarding dispute over completion of a book by Olson, 1964-1965 (Box 9:229)
  - Olson, Charles The Special View of History (edited by Ann Charters)
    - (Box 9:230)
    - finished book, 1970 (Box 9:230)
    - copy of TSS, 2 sets corrected galleys (galley 1 and galley 5), TSS for epigraphs, 1970 (Box 9:231)
    - 2 sets galleys (one with corrections), 3 sets page proofs, 1970 (Box 9:232)
    - advance copy, printing notes, partial proofs, proofs of promotional mailer, 2 photos (1 used for cover), 1970 (Box 9:233)
    - page proofs, printing correspondence and bills, 1970-1975 (Box 9:234)
    - correspondence with Charles Boer (Olson estate), 1970-1971 (Box 9:235)
    - cover design, cover paste-up, galleys, 1970 (Box 16:441)
  - Palmer, Doug
    - correspondence and records detailing sales of Basta and Moon Services (works not published by Oyez), 1967-1968 (Box 9:236)
  - Palmer, Doug In Quire
    - early correspondence, 1968 (Box 9:237)
    - TSS and printing instructions from author, contract, 1970 (Box 9:238)
    - second version TSS, correspondence, MS of author's note, ca. 1973 (Box 9:239)
    - two sets of galleys, two sets of proofs, 1973 (Box 9:240)
  - Parkinson, Thomas Thanatos: Earth Poems
    - galleys, contract, correspondence, secondary correspondence, printer's bill, 1965-1980 (Box 9:241)
    - production paste-ups, copies of proofs, 1977 (Box 17:464)
    - plate negatives in layout paste-up, 1977 (Box 17:465)
  - Parkinson, Thomas
    - TSS of poems titled Forgeries (not published by Oyez), undated (Box 9:242)
  - Parkinson, Thomas "From the Grand Chartreuse"
    - 2 finished copies of Oyez Keepsake for New Year's, 1981 (Box 9:243)
  - Rodriguez-Nieto, Catherine, (ed.) Firelight: Three Latin-American Poets
    - TSS (includes Photocopy pages), printing bill, 2 pcs. original art, design and layout materials, review, 1975-1976 (Box 9:244)
    - production paste-ups, copies of proofs, 1976 (Box 17:453)
  - Ruddy, William Braille for a Storm of Loss
    - 2 copies TSS (1 from printer), 1 pc. correspondence, cassette tape of poems read by the author, ca. 1978 (Box 9:245)
    - camera ready copy with 9 pcs. original line drawings, 1978 (Box 9:246)
    - camera ready copy with 9 pcs. original line drawings, undated (Box 9:247)
    - correspondence, 2 sets proofs ('silverprint' and 'check' copies), 2 reviews, cover design, cover proof, 1978-1979 (Box 9:248)
  - Say, Allen The Nose (Oyez Christmas Keepsake, 1973)
    - 2 finished copies (handsewn, in mailing envelopes), TSS, galleys, 2 dummies, correspondence, 1973 (Box 10:249)
  - Seelye, John "BOEMB"
    - printed broadside poem, 1965 (Box 10:250)
  - Silberg, Richard The Reckoning
    - galleys, correspondence, printer's bill, 1979 (Box 10:251)
  - Simon, John Oliver Roads to Dawn Lake
    - 2 sets galleys (1 set corrected by author), correspondence, 1968 (Box 10:252)
    - galleys pasted into notebook (VERY FRAGILE), 1968 (Box 10:253)
    - correspondence, set of F+G proofs, review, 1968-1972 (Box 10:254)
  - Simon, John Oliver Picture of Red Bull Striding (not published by Oyez)
    - copy of TSS and 1 pc. correspondence from author, 1970 (Box 10:255)
  - Södergran, Edith / Charters, Samuel We Women
    - corrected proofs, cover photo, Photocopy proof set, F & G proofs, jacket proof, correspondence, 1977 (Box 10:256)
    - camera ready paste-up, 1977 (Box 10:257)
  - Spicer, Jack A Book of Music (White Rabbit Publication)
    - TSS prepared by Andrea Wyatt (with printer's note), undated (Box 10:258)
  - Spicer, Jack Language (White Rabbit Reprint)
    - First printing dissected, printer's correspondence, promotional cards, 1969 (Box 10:259)
  - Spicer, Jack Book of Magazine Verse (White Rabbit Reprint)
    - First printing dissected, printer's correspondence, 1969 (Box 10:260)
    - correspondence relating to Spicer estate, reprints, ca. 1969-1981 (Box 10:261)
  - Tichborne, Chidiock "Tichborne's Elegy, Written in the Tower Before His Execution, 1586" (published by Cody's Books)
    - Print of Broadside Poem, ca. 1965? (Box 10:262)
  - Torregian, Sotère The Wounded Mattress
    - Correspondence, includes 4 pcs. correspondence from Philip Lamantia, contract, 1969-1973 (Box 10:263)
    - TSS, copy of TSS, photocopies of original art by author, ca. 1965 (Box 10:264)
    - galleys, page proofs, sample pages, cover proof, 1970 (Box 10:265)
    - 2 sets page proofs, illustration notes, 1 pc. original art by author, cover photo, 1970 (Box 10:266)
    - jacket paste-up (Box 17:454)
  - Torregian, Sotère
    - Secondary Correspondence, includes unpublished poetry TSS, ca. 1976 (Box 10:267)
  - Torregian, Kathleen Teague
    - unpublished poetry TSS, 1970 (Box 10:268)
  - Transtormer, Thomas / Charters, Samuel Baltics
    - copy of TSS, correspondence, printer's bill, review clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 10:269)
    - set of first galleys, partial proofs, cover photo, jacket art proofs, 1975 (Box 10:270)
    - corrected page proofs, blank dummy, cover proof, 1975 (Box 10:271)
    - camera-ready proof set, 1 pc. correspondence, 1975 (Box 10:272)
  - Vinograd, Julia Revolution and Other Poems
    - Four sets galleys, sample pages, blank dummy, 2 sets page proofs, 1970 (Box 10:273)
    - TSS, correspondence, budgeting notes, 1970 (Box 10:274)
  - Vinograd, Julia Berkeley Street Cannibals
    - printer's bills, review, 1976 (Box 10:275)
  - Welch, Lew On Out
    - unused cover proof, contract, correspondence, reviews, 1965 (Box 10:276)
    - first edition (Stapled proof in wrapper), TSS, corrected galleys, 1965 (Box 10:277)
    - correspondence, copy used for photo offset of second printing, 1965 (Box 10:278)
  - Wyatt, Andrea Three Rooms
    - correspondence, TSS, 3 sets galleys, page proofs, F & G proofs, dummy, cover proof, design notes, review clipping, 1969-1972 (Box 10:279)
  - Wyatt, Andrea "Flowers Were Left There"
    - Four variant proofs of broadside poem, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 10:280)
  - Wyatt, Andrea A Bibliography of Works by Larry Eigner
    - TSS with note, printer's correspondence, 1970 (Box 10:281)
  - Wyatt, Andrea Poems of the Morning, Poems of the Storm
    - Poems of the Morning, Poems of the Storm, variant TSS, galleys and correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 10:282)
- Series II: Press Correspondence, undated, 1964-1986
  - "A", undated (Box 11:283)
  - Allen, Donald (2 pcs), 1964 (Box 11:284)
  - "B", undated (Box 11:285)
  - Bartlett, Lee, 1974-1975, 1980 (Box 11:286)
  - Bertholf, Robert, 1978 (Box 11:287)
  - Bertolino, James, 1970-1973 (Box 11:288)
  - Black Sparrow Press -- John Martin, 1965-1969 (Box 11:289)
  - Bronk, William, 1965-1967 (Box 11:290)
  - Broughton, James, 1968-1969 (Box 11:291)
  - Butterick, George, 1969-1971 (Box 11:292)
  - "C", undated (Box 11:293)
  - Campo, Allan, 1965-1973 (Box 11:294)
  - CCLM -- Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines, 1968-1973 (Box 11:295)
  - Cohn, Marguerite -- House of Books, 1964-1967 (Box 11:296)
  - COSMEP -- Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers, 1968-1986 (Box 11:297)
  - Creeley, Robert, 1965 (Box 11:298)
  - Curtis, Gordon, 1966-1967 (Box 11:299)
  - "D", undated (Box 11:300)
  - Dillon, Richard "Dick", ca. 1976-1980 (Box 11:301)
  - "E", undated (Box 11:302)
  - "F" - "G", undated (Box 11:303)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence (1 pc.), 1965 (Box 11:304)
  - Ferrini, Vincent (2 pcs.), 1965, 1968 (Box 11:305)
  - "H", undated (Box 11:306)
  - "I" - "J" - "K", undated (Box 11:307)
  - "L", undated (Box 11:308)
  - Laughlin, James - New Directions, 1966-1976 (Box 11:309)
  - Levertov, Denise, 1967-1972 (Box 11:310)
  - "M", undated (Box 11:311)
  - Mackintosh, Graham, 1970-1981 (Box 12:312)
  - Malanga, Gerard, 1966 (Box 12:313)
  - Moskowitz, Paul, 1984 (Box 12:314)
  - "N" - "O" - "P" - "Q", undated (Box 12:315)
  - Phoenix Book Shop - Marshall Clements, Robert Wilson, 1965, 1970 (Box 12:316)
  - "R", undated (Box 12:317)
  - "S", undated (Box 12:318)
  - Saroyan, Aram, 1965, 1977 (Box 12:319)
  - Snyder, Gary (2 pcs.), 1965 (Box 12:320)
  - "T" - "U" - "V" (Box 12:321)
  - Unicorn Book Shop - Alan Brilliant, Jack Shoemaker, 1966-1976 (Box 12:322)
  - "W", undated (Box 12:323)
  - Whalen, Philip (1 pc.), 1965 (Box 12:324)
  - "X" - "Y" - "Z", undated (Box 12:325)
  - Correspondents Not Identified, ca. 1965-1978 (Box 12:326)
  - Correspondence regarding print ads - Poetry, Nation, New York Review of Books, 1965-1969 (Box 12:327)
  - Secondary Correspondence with Universities and Libraries, 1967-1981 (Box 12:328)
  - Gift Acknowledgements from Universities and Libraries, 1966-1977 (Box 12:329)
  - Correspondence Regarding Catalogs and Indices of Small Presses, 1970-1976 (Box 12:330)
  - Marketing of Small Press Publications (not Oyez), undated (Box 12:331-334)
  - Mailings from Literary Magazines, undated (Box 12:335)
  - AAP - Academy of American Poets Press Releases, 1977-1979 (Box 12:336)
  - Small Press Publications not related to Oyez, undated (Box 13:337)
  - Announcements for Literary Events (not related to Oyez) (Box 13:338-339)
  - Manuscript Submission
    - Ajay, Stephen (Box 13:340)
    - Atkins, Ruth (Box 13:341)
    - Auster, Paul (Box 13:342)
    - Barnes, Keith (Box 13:343)
    - Bett, Stephen (Box 13:344)
    - Cahill, Patrick (Box 13:345)
    - Caplin, Loren Paul (Box 13:346)
    - Cassidy, Lelia B. (Box 13:347)
    - Cole, David (Box 13:348)
    - Collom, Jack (Box 13:349)
    - Cloutier, David (Box 13:350)
    - Dahlin, Barbara (Box 13:351)
    - Dobel, Ken (Box 13:352)
    - Fritzinger, Dennis (Box 13:353)
    - Gelfand, Jim (Box 13:354)
    - Goethe, Diane (Box 13:355)
    - Greenberg, Judith Anne (Box 13:356)
    - Grieder, Ted (Box 13:357)
    - Hamilton, Fritz (Box 13:358)
    - Hays, John (Box 13:359)
    - Henderson, Edward (Box 13:360)
    - Henig, Suzanne (Box 13:361)
    - Henkin, Bill (Box 13:362)
    - Howden, Michael (Box 13:363)
    - Jackson, William (Box 13:364)
    - Johnson, Nick (Box 13:365)
    - Kruglick, Lewis (Box 13:366)
    - Kunz, Lennie (Box 13:367)
    - Madigan, Michael (Box 13:368)
    - Martini, Sister Galen (Box 14:369)
    - Moritz, Albert F. (Box 14:370)
    - Moscrip, Carol (Box 14:371)
    - Mosley, Maya (Box 14:372)
    - Murphy, Joseph Frank (Box 14:373)
    - Murphy, Tom (Box 14:374)
    - Novak, Helga M. (tr. by Ann Maria Celona) (Box 14:375)
    - Porter, Arnold (Box 14:376)
    - Petersen, Gail (Box 14:377)
    - Ratner, Rochelle (Box 14:378)
    - Rogers, Daniel John (Box 14:379)
    - Ross, David S. (Box 14:380)
    - Rudge, Mary (Box 14:381)
    - Russell, Daniel (2 versions) (Box 14:382)
    - Rivlin, Michael (Box 14:383)
    - Skinner, John (Box 14:384)
    - Smith, Joe (Box 14:385)
    - Steingesser, Martin (Box 14:386)
    - Tavolieri, Mike (Box 14:387)
    - Terr, Leonard (Box 14:388)
    - Townley, Rod (I) (Box 14:389-390)
    - Vangelisti, Paul (Box 14:391)
    - Ventadour, Fanny (Box 14:392)
    - Viglini, Janelle (Box 14:393)
    - Walker, Richard (Box 14:394)
    - Wampler, Martin (Box 14:395)
    - Wilson, Robert Dean (Box 14:396)
    - Yates, Robin (Box 14:397)
    - Zaller, Robert (Box 14:398)
    - Zero, Frank (Box 14:399)
    - Zipse, Erwin (Box 14:400)
- Series III: Press Ephemera, undated, 1965-1986
  - Materials for Unproduced 'Festschrift' for Graham Mackintosh (various correspondents, including David Meltzer, Larry Eigner, Sotère Torregian, and Mary Fabilli), 1971 (Box 15:401)
  - Submission for unproduced 'festschrift' for Graham Mackintosh by "NTDS", ca. 1976 (Box 17:459)
  - 2 copies of broadside with poem "The Seers" by Richard Korn and 2 short poems by Orlanda Brugnola, 1971 (Box 15:402)
  - Announcements and Mailings, plus Christmas card by David Meltzer, ca. 1965 (Box 15:403)
  - Reviews and clippings not related to single projects, ca. 1970-1975 (Box 15:404)
  - Flyers and advertisements by Oyez, White Rabbit, ca. 1970 (Box 15:405)
  - Advertising Materials, Booklists, and Print Ads by Oyez, ca. 1969-1972 (Box 15:406)
  - Serendipity Books Catalogs (Oyez distributor), 1975-1977 (Box 15:407)
  - Photos of Bob Hawley, Doug Palmer, Sister Mary Norbert Körte, undated (Box 15:408)
  - Photos (not identified), undated (Box 15:409)
  - Programs from Events attended by Hawley, 1968, 1976 (Box 15:410)
  - Robert Hawley's Certificate of Ordination in Universal Life Church, 1974 (Box 15:411)
  - Typesetting Catalogs, ca. 1975, 1986 (Box 15:412)
  - Proofs and TSS for announcement of broadside series, 1965 (Box 15:413)
  - Notes and Correspondence dealing with Hawley's role as agent for the sale of Kenneth Patchen's archive (Box 15:414)
  - Materials and Correspondence regarding Rounce and Coffin Western Books Exhibition, 1968 (Box 15:415)
  - Sales and Payment Ledger (Broadside Series), 1974 (Box 15:416)
- Series IV: Business Records, 1964-1981
  - Sales and Payment Ledger (Broadside Series), 1964-1966 (Box 15:417)
  - Sales Ledger (Various Titles), 1965-1968 (Box 15:418)
  - Sales Ledger (Everson -- Robinson Jeffers, Ann Charters), 1968-1969 (Box 15:419)
  - Checkbooks (2 ledgers), 1966-1981 (Box 15:420)
  - Sales/ Transactions -- Orders and Receipts, 1964-1966 (Box 15:421)
  - Sales/ Transactions -- Orders and Receipts, 1964-1967 (Box 15:422)
  - Sales/ Transactions -- Orders and Receipts, 1966-1967 (Box 15:423)
  - Sales/ Transactions -- Orders and Receipts, 1966-1970 (Box 15:424)
  - Correspondence/ Transactions with Printers (includes Cranium Press, West Coast Print Center, Braun-Brumfield, Edwards Brothers, Banta West), 1970-1979 (Box 15:425)
  - R. R. Bowker Books in Print Checklist, ca. 1980 (Box 15:426)
- Series V: Printing Blocks, undated
  Engravings and woodblocks in this series are packed loosely. Most are marked with stickers to correspond with the dealer's catalog. The table below will help with cross-referencing blocks and book projects:
  - Identified Blocks (Box 18)
    - II.d. David Meltzer The Process (1 pc.)
    - II.i. David Meltzer The Process (1 pc.)
    - IV.f Bram Dijkstra Faces in Skin (8 pcs)
    - V.k. Lew Welch On Out (1 pc.)
    - VI.h. Lawrence McGaugh A Fifth Sunday (1 pc.)
    - VII.e. Thomas Parkinson Thanatos: Earth Poems
    - X.k. Mary Fabilli The Old Ones (5 pcs.)
    - XI.x. William Everson (Brother Antoninus ) Single Source (2 pcs.)
    - XI.y. William Everson (Brother Antoninus ) Single Source (2 pcs.)
    - XII.e. David Kherdian Biographical Sketch and Descriptive Checklist of Gary Snyder (1 pc.)
    - Philip Lamantia Touch of the Marvelous (1 pc.)
    - Sister Mary Norbert Körte Hymn to the Gentle Sun (1 pc.)
    - Robert Duncan The Years as Catches (1 pc.)
    - Robert Duncan Of the War (1 pc.)